FILING FOR LOVE
2013 YEONHYANG TEMPLE CUISINE RETREAT
NOV. 15 TO 22, 2013
MOTHER JOO KYUNG-HEE,
REMEMBERED BY JOO IN-A
Mom's resting place
has such crisp air.
Mister, untie me!
Let me go right now!
What are you doing to me?
Mister, let me go!
I have to get out of here!
- I have to leave!
- Mom!
- I have to get out!
Untie me right now!
What are you doing? No! Don't!
- Hold on to her tight.
- No! Let me go!
- Grab her tightly!
- No!
Jumping from there
will cause too much trouble.
You'll land smack on a hiking trail.
It must've been a long walk up here.
Why don't you put that will
and energy toward trying to live?
Enjoy the clean air and go home.
The walk down is much nicer.
I think you missed the last bus.
Are there really no more buses today?
Where are you headed?
- I'll drop you off.
- I'm too afraid
to accept a ride from someone
who just tried to end his life.
No, thank you.
You have a point.
Excuse me.
I hope to see you again alive.
Hello.
I'm Lee Tae-kwon, the new recruit.
I hope we all get along.
There's one last person to introduce.
Joo In-a beat her competition
for first place
among her batch of new recruits.
She's a true elite.
I'll show what a first-place recruit
can do. Thank you.
I hope we work well together.
Cheers.
Good job.
Why is this group so silent?
Ms. Joo, pour Mr. Jeon a drink.
Oh, sure.
So I heard you're the son
of Haemu Group's president.
A third-generation chaebol heir
I’d only heard about.
Then you must know
I'm not valued much as a son.
Was that why you were struggling
when we crossed paths back then?
I hope we work well together
Manager Jeon Jae-yeol.
I really hoped to see you again.
I'm glad I chose to live.
What do you mean?
Mr. Jeon headed this project
from the initial planning stage.
It just need to be signed
to be approved
and you want me
to omit Mr. Jeon's name?
Ms. Joo, you need to see
the big picture here.
Don't you see his stepbrother
has been taking all the credit
since he joined the company?
So what? Are you saying that's okay?
- If the president were to hear...
- Oh, come on.
All this is possible
because the president is allowing it.
You've heard, haven't you?
About Mr. Jeon's birth mother.
He won't ever make it.
We must side
with his younger brother.
Fly to Dubai and close the deal.
There's a flight in two hours.
- You need to hurry.
- In-a.
This will only get you in trouble.
This isn't even my project.
It's the company's.
Still, it's too unfair and wrong.
You did all the hard work.
It's enough for me
that you know that.
Everyone's too cruel.
They're so mean and nasty.
In-a.
I swear
I'll protect you
for as long as I'm here.
Whatever happens,
even if the sky falls...
I'll be on your side, Jae-yeol.
This is so darn infuriating.
So you were a couple.
We were once a couple.
Why did you break up?
Just because
he found someone
within his league to marry
and I wanted to live
a life of my own.
It's one of those boring
and obvious reasons.
It's all in the past.
Are you sure of that?
What does that mean?
There was a tip-off
claiming you were having
an inappropriate workplace affair.
That's you and the VP, isn't it?
You came back.
It has been a long time,
Vice President Jeon.
I missed you.
I think it was the day
I returned to the head office.
He was just pleased to see me again.
It didn't mean anything else.
It didn't mean anything?
The situation I just witnessed
would signify otherwise.
Is this the vice president's
one-sided feeling?
Or is there
something left between you two?
I don't want you to come here
whenever you please.
- In-a.
- Take your hands off me.
Let go.
The VP and I...
He's an executive,
and I'm just his subordinate.
That's all it is.
I have no residual feelings
toward him.
To be honest, I suspected you
after I got the tip-off.
So I investigated about you
and tailed you.
I even followed you home
for a stakeout.
I knew it.
There's a reason you're the ace.
I never imagined
the guy would turn out to be the VP.
So, what now?
What's your conclusion
as the handler of PM cases?
I don't know.
I want to believe
everything you say at face value
that it's all in the past
and however the VP feels about you
you feel nothing for him now.
But...
I think it's my heart
that wants to believe that.
Give me some time.
I'll think about it
as cool-headed as possible.
EPISODE 7:
TO HER LOVER
- Five packs of soju cups.
- And five packs of paper cups.
- Five of those.
- Two packs of plastic spoons.
- Oh, and seltzer water.
- Seltzer water?
- Yes.
- We didn't order any.
- For highballs.
Okay, add seltzer to the list.
And then...
Mr. Moo, can you stay still?
I'm finding it hard to focus already.
I guess I'm excited. We haven't
held any workshop in a while.
I did some thinking, you see.
No workshop is complete
without a barbecue.
It wouldn't feel right.
Don't you think, White Blood Cell?
You're right. It wouldn't feel right.
- Right?
- Hae-young.
Eleven people will drive there,
and the rest will take the bus.
Okay.
Send a list of names
- to the bus driver.
- Okay.
When did you two
get close enough to speak casually?
You caught on real slow.
Mr. Cha, did you finish
your tasks for the day?
Why are you over here?
Did you text the whole office?
I will right now.
Gosh, I'm sick of your nagging.
Hae-young. We should order
pork belly and pork neck.
Okay, fine.
- Will you order some?
- Yes.
- Yes, buy some pork. A big chunk.
- Just pork neck.
Assistant Manager Noh Ki-jun, is it?
Can he be trusted?
He's an arrogant punk.
He's definitely not
the submissive type.
What did he mean?
That something that can't work
still can work.
What cannot work
and what can work?
You're Haemu Group's vice president.
Why would you mind a lowly employee?
You must have
other important matters.
Ms. Joo.
- Yes, Hae-young.
- Haemu issued new credit cards.
Give me your old one. I'll cut it up.
- It's in my bag. I'll get it.
- Okay, thank you.
See?
Something that can't work
still can work.
Does that issue have to wait
until the next meeting?
It is a bit too early to bring up
although what you want
is what matters most.
You met with Director Han, right?
Yes, I did.
Noh Ki-jun.
Will you knock first?
I'm cooking ramyeon.
Do you want some?
No.
- Don't you dare ask for a bite.
- Hey, A-jeong.
What's your VP like?
Why do you say "your VP"?
He's yours, too.
You're right.
He's my boss, too.
Why are you
suddenly asking about him?
I thought you were
trying to figure out Joo In-a.
You rushed out saying
you wanted to figure out
your relationship with her.
Did you figure it out?
I figured out one thing for sure.
That she's a darn tough woman.
- What does that mean?
- I don't know. Forget it.
Enjoy your ramyeon.
What the heck?
HAEMU GROUP
2025 HAEMU GROUP
STRATEGIC PLANNING JOINT WORKSHOP
HAEMU TRAINING CENTER
- Oh, dear.
- My goodness.
Gosh. Are we doing a barbecue?
Of course, Ms. Joo.
A barbecue is a must at a workshop.
I like the way you think, Mr. Moo.
- I'll help with the stuff.
- What?
- No!
- Don't!
Let me pretend to be
an easygoing boss.
- But...
- Oh, gosh...
That must weigh at least 20kg.
She's pretty strong.
- Move the boxes now.
- Yes, sir.
You have a clinical condition
of acting tough.
STRATEGIC PLANNING JOINT WORKSHOP
A TIME TO CONNECT TO GROW
The Planning Team.
Human Resources.
And the Audit Team.
I just said your team names,
and I'm shuddering in fear.
You work so hard
to keep our company going.
At this workshop
I hope you can forget
your strenuous workplace
and relax and have a good time.
Hang on. Why aren't you in bed?
Isn't it almost midnight
where you are?
I'm exhausted. Mom nags too much.
Can't you just do as she says?
She said she's been having headaches.
Okay?
Sleep well.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Mr. Ahn, you should
take time off work soon
to fly to the US to see your family.
I didn't know you were watching.
It's a pleasing sight.
Are the others getting ready
for the next program?
Oh, we'd initially planned
a team-building exercise
but the two team heads said
playing a sport is the best way
to boost teamwork.
2025 HAEMU
STRATEGIC PLANNING JOINT WORKSHOP
Warm up well and properly
so you don't get injured.
Can't we watch an educational video
instead of playing futsal?
Haven't you heard, Ms. Yoon?
Ms. Joo said the MVP of today's match
can take the day off tomorrow.
What are you doing?
My gosh. What's gotten into you now?
Why are you suddenly so eager now?
- Faster!
- Goodness.
I see you don't exercise much.
Okay, everyone.
Both men and women will play
- so be sure no one gets hurt, okay?
- Yes, ma'am.
Don't do anything
too aggressive like tackling.
- Let's put safety first.
- Okay.
We can't do that
if we're playing a competitive sport.
It's all about winning.
Take one of these beforehand.
- Let's build some energy first.
- Thank you.
- "Build energy"?
Energy is an asset, too, these days.
We must save up when we can
to use when we must.
- Thank you.
- At a moment like this.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Wait, what's going on?
Are you not going to share?
Isn't this against the rules?
Isn't this a foul?
Hello, sir!
- Hello.
- Hello, sir.
Mr. Jeon, sir.
I thought you'd left
after the opening speech.
I heard you'd planned something fun,
so I decided to come cheer you on.
Will you be rooting
for the Audit Team?
Of course not.
You'll be cheering for HR, right?
Let's see. I'm thinking of supporting
whichever is the winning team.
That'll be our Audit Team.
- That's no fun.
- What?
Ignoring the process
and siding with the winner.
Isn't that uncool?
You speak as if you're the winner.
Yes.
Because I will win.
Mr. Noh is excessively competitive.
I don't think we can be teammates.
How about we compete for real?
Sir, are you really joining
the match?
You have a meeting at 3 p.m.
Cancel it.
Kick it! Score a goal!
What the...
- Shoot.
- Stop! Stop it!
- Ki-jun!
- Watch out!
Kick it.
Mr. Jeon! No!
Mr. Jeon, are you all right?
Are you okay, sir?
I told you to play nice!
What should we do about you?
What got into Mr. Noh?
Doesn't he know he should give in?
Maybe he wants to be the MVP
to take tomorrow off.
At this rate,
he might lose his job for good.
It must be your leather shoes.
- Wear my trainers.
- No, it's fine.
No, please, sir. Wear mine.
That would be best for us all.
- I'm fine.
- Mr. Noh is going too far.
What the... Did you see that?
That was a foul!
- Referee! Come on!
- Not a foul!
- Get back up.
- It's not a foul.
He didn't do anything wrong.
That was just a bump.
Keep playing.
That was uncalled for. It was...
Sir, you can go ahead and score.
- No, wait. Time out!
- What?
Sir, go ahead. Score a goal.
- What are you doing?
- Time out!
You caught it all, didn't you?
You filmed it, didn't you?
Referee, VAR.
Let's watch the instant replay.
- Boo.
- No, forget it.
- Let's review the footage.
- You're being a nuisance!
You're a nuisance.
That's uncool. Stop it.
Let's keep things going!
- Let's play!
- What the heck?
Wait! That's not fair!
Come on. Get the ball.
- Bring it this way!
- No!
Are you all right?
You said you'd win at all costs.
You must feel let down.
Not exactly. It wasn't a fair match.
Ms. Joo tripped you up on purpose.
Let me apologize instead.
In-a can be like that.
What do you mean by "like that"?
Oh, do you mean she has long legs?
Do you have anyone like that?
Someone who always takes your side
no matter what happens.
Actually, we go way back.
Sir.
Are you hiding something?
You speak too much as if to deflect.
It looks like you're trying
to hide something from me.
Mr. Choi got you a change of clothes.
Shall I cancel
your evening plans, too?
I live
with a guy right now.
Ms. Park.
The nice guy you said you lived with.
Is it Mr. Noh Ki-jun?
What's with this?
What the...
Are you trying to smash the thing?
Come and sit down.
Take a seat.
- Is it this foot?
- What the heck?
It's this foot.
- Let me see.
- No...
It's not that swollen.
Don't be silly.
Look at this side.
My ankle is usually slim like this.
What a crybaby.
You hurt me
and now you're treating me?
You tripped me up on purpose,
didn't you?
How could you sabotage a teammate?
Would the VP look bad
if he didn't get to score today?
Why do you care so much about him?
Your career at Haemu would've ended
if you'd gone any further.
You should know
where to draw the line
in front of your coworkers,
especially HR.
Don't you know
they'd have avenged the VP
even if the VP himself
didn't complain?
Goodness.
You've worked long enough
to know how things work.
Why were you so childish out there?
So that means you took my side
and not the VP's.
I'm not on anyone's side.
I just did what a superior would do
to protect her subordinate.
- Okay.
- What do you mean by "okay"?
Your PM case.
I think I can conclude it now.
- Just like that?
- Other similar cases were closed
without disciplinary action
when the subject denied the charges
and no other definite proof
could be found.
I couldn't decide
whether I should investigate further
and drag the VP
to the interview room to grill him.
I realized something today.
The way you both feel for each other
is different.
I believe you.
I want to believe
how you feel.
How do you think
I feel?
What you did today...
Was that really
only just to protect
your subordinate?
I showed you.
Some things can work.
I don't care how long it takes.
Take a good look at your feelings.
I'll wait.
So Ms. Song, you were in the shower
and it seemed like someone
filmed the shower booth, right?
Yes, someone was clearly filming
with their cell phone.
What did the culprit look like?
Did you get a glimpse?
I just got a glimpse
of the person's back
and he was wearing
the men's T-shirt for our department.
- So disgusting.
- That's crazy.
An inside job.
This is the lodging,
so there are no CCTVs around.
Do you remember anything else?
He must be using a white cell phone.
What I saw was a white rectangle.
Like a white cell phone?
- I guess so.
- It's so gross.
Everyone has that, right?
This looks like
a simple job to handle
as long as
the male employees cooperate.
And do what? Check their phones?
Let's check only the white phones
and he might have hidden
the phone he used to film with
so we should check each room
for people's luggage.
- You don't need to go that far...
- We need to check for sure.
It may be an inconvenience,
but please cooperate.
- Goodness.
- Goodness, no. We should do it.
We cannot rule out the possibility
that the culprit is the Audit Team.
To make it fair, let's have
one from Audit and one from HR
conduct only the necessary amount
of verification.
All right.
Mr. Ahn, can you represent the HR?
You're known to be upright and proper
- so no one will complain.
- Yes, I understand.
- Ms. Kim?
- Mr. Ahn, actually...
You two look great together.
- I didn't see anything.
- Yes, okay.
Come on, Mr. Cha.
You can't do this
as a member of the Audit Team.
These were...
These were from the barbecue.
Never mind, Hyun-kyu.
Let's give the used ones to him.
You can have these at home.
Thanks.
We searched through
the women's rooms just in case
but couldn't find anything.
We need to do everything we can.
Are there no CCTVs near the entrance?
Once the day breaks, I'll ask
the management and check right away.
Anyway, you all worked hard
until this late.
Let's go back and get some rest.
All right. Great work.
Mr. Ahn, you dropped this.
- Oh.
- Huh?
You smoke, Mr. Ahn? Since when?
Once every now and then.
I smoke in secret.
There's no need to smoke in secret
when you're at work.
Do you want
to step out with me for a second?
He must be using a white cell phone.
No, I plan to quit very soon.
Thanks, Mr. Noh. I'll have it.
I don't want to give it back.
- Why not?
- If you want to quit
you should do it right away.
Let me give you a hand.
It's okay.
I'll quit starting tomorrow.
No way. You need to make
these decisions right away.
Mr. Noh, do not give it back.
- No, ma'am.
- Gosh, you two are quite the tease.
Give it back, Mr. Noh!
Goodness, yes. Don't try to control
what someone else likes to do.
And cigarettes
are quite expensive these days.
Yes!
This thing?
What the...
Why? What is it?
Is this a camera?
Mr. Ahn!
I can't believe this!
Have you lost your mind?
Damn it.
Look at all these.
Looks like you didn’t care
the time or place when filming these.
From the elevator ride to the office
in-house cafeteria, restroom
and the subway ride back home.
Wait, how did you take this?
No!
Did you install cameras
under the staff members' desks?
This is exactly that angle!
Well, Ms. Joo, it's...
How can you do this
to your colleagues
whom you work with every single day?
What do you take them for?
All right. I get it.
But I am fully cooperating, right?
Blowing this up
won't do any good for the company.
And it'll put our department
in a different position.
- Think of our company's image, too.
- Sure, those are important.
Our position and the company's image.
That's why...
we should blow this up
as much as we can.
While other companies
are busy trying to cover up
their in-house sexual assaults,
we'll be the company
that punished
a spycam offender harshly
to become a great example.
Wait...
Today
I plan to eat at the cafeteria
for the first time in a while.
Yes, sir. I'll call them right away.
No.
I'll go downstairs now.
I don't like eating in the cafeteria.
We have to eat so we can wrap up
Mr. Ahn's case and submit the report.
Eat up.
We have to eat something delicious
to work more efficiently
and to put together a better report.
But this is delicious.
It's so good.
What?
May I join you?
Sure, we didn't rent out the place.
Have a seat.
Jae-yeol is at the cafeteria?
Yes, on top of that,
he sat with Ms. Joo
and Mr. Noh Ki-jun
of Audit Team Three
so it was a huge deal
in the Audit Team's office.
My brother can be pretty sly, too.
Well, I got to eat with Doo-gi,
the best
of Audit Team One, didn't I?
It's an honor, Mr. Jeon.
How's work these days?
Were you in charge
of our subsidiaries?
Yes, I'm now in charge of the steels
and the pharmaceuticals.
You're in charge
of the pharmaceuticals?
If you're doing that now,
who used to be in charge?
May I ask why you wish to know that?
Well, it's not a big deal.
Yesterday, I drank with people
from the pharmaceutical division.
They said the Audit Team
used to pester them to death
but not anymore these days.
So I was wondering
if there was a power trip back then
or if things
aren't working smoothly right now.
But I guess
someone else was handling it.
Yes, sir.
I heard Mr. Noh played
a big part
in the recent spycam incident.
Yes, well, it's my job.
He seems quite competent.
Why did you put him in charge of PM?
I'm the type
who's good at everything that I do.
Gosh, so delicious.
You two have
a special relationship, don't you?
Last time, I saw you two together
by chance
while dropping Ms. Park off
at her place.
Oh, is it discourteous of me
to bring up something this personal
in front of your direct superior?
Yes, it is discourteous.
And what's so bad about that?
The housing price in Seoul
has skyrocketed
so it's nice and economical.
You already knew?
Of course.
She's been to our place, too.
Is that so?
Since when did our company
begin to visit our employees at home?
I'll have to ask to be excused.
I was in the middle of work.
Sit.
We're sitting here at the same table
so don't you think it's basic manners
to get up together?
You have a point.
I'll go with you, Mr. Noh.
I almost forgot my manners
and sent you back alone.
We were initially
in the middle of eating together.
Please enjoy your lunch, you two.
Let's go.
Come on. Let's go.
- Isn't it good?
- It is.
We should never waste any food,
but I couldn't help it. What a shame.
Anyway, this toast is really good.
Is this your first time trying it?
That place has been around forever.
When I was new, the only fun I had
at work was getting this
on my way to work
and eating it in the office.
Did you get one
for the vice president?
I don't know.
He must be furious, right?
How am I going to keep my career
in the future?
Will you take responsibility
and protect your subordinate?
So why did you act so cheekily?
I mean, he was way too immature
for someone who's a vice president.
Anyway, I can tell after today
that he's definitely still into you.
Then what? Do you want to conduct
an additional investigation?
No, you aren't into him,
so it doesn't matter.
I guess some people remember
their old relationship like the rose
from The Little Prince.
- What do you mean by that?
- Don't you know it?
The Little Prince comes to Earth
and sees many roses
that are exactly the same-looking.
Yet he returns to the planet
where the rose
he spent time with lives.
The Little Prince returns?
Doesn't he live
with the fox on Earth?
No, he returns to his planet.
He wants to be responsible
for the rose he cultivated.
No, he remains on Earth.
No, he returns.
Do you want to make a bet?
Bet? I'm in.
We aren't betting on a wish,
but a penalty.
Sure.
"I'm returning to the star tonight."
See? It means
he's returning to his planet.
What? This is really sad.
Why did I remember the story
as a happy ending? What is this?
You must've interpreted this
as a happy ending back then.
Why did he want to leave Earth
after the trouble of getting there?
So I won, right?
You must've been
an avid reader of children's tales.
Admit to your defeat
and face your penalty.
Admitted. What's the penalty?
Now, what can I do here
to turn this into a cruel fairy tale?
What is it?
Hey, Ms. Joo has finally gone cuckoo
in her head.
Excuse me, Ms. Joo.
Your hair...
What about it?
Isn't it adorable?
I've been into these things lately.
Get back to work.
ART CLASS DIRECTOR
Thank you.
That's cute.
What in the world is that hairpin?
Yes, right. I still had this on?
How embarrassing.
That's new.
Is that the recent trend?
No, it was a gift from someone
as a penalty.
Anyway.
I don't have to come
as a model anymore?
What's going on? Am I getting fired?
I should've hired you officially
and paid you.
The business has been slow,
so I've been shameless.
Don't say that.
I did it because I wanted to.
And you already know
that I needed this.
Do you still need it?
I've known you a long time, In-a.
And lately, I've been thinking
that you might not need
this time anymore.
You've been laughing a lot.
- Me?
- Yes, and you seem to be at peace.
Tell me.
You're seeing someone, right?
Is it the one
who gave you that hairpin?
No, this is way too...
You're the flower of the Audit Team,
so why don't you put a flower on?
All right.
A pig.
Next, a rabbit.
Look to the side.
- I can't.
- What do you mean? Why not?
He's someone at work.
In another country, there is
this phrase about dating at work.
"Don't go number two where you eat."
It means it's that insane.
Why not? It's better than
holding it in and getting sick.
I'm saying, who cares
if you do something crazy?
Didn't you think this job was
also crazy before you did it?
But after trying it
it became the only escape
in your everyday life.
Don't put a limit on yourself.
Only when you break the limit
will you find new joy.
Hey, Director.
You're good with words.
You didn't know?
RECREATIONAL ART CLASS
TONIGHT AT 9 P.M.
Have I always been this pretty?
You are pretty.
AUDIT RESULT
You didn't seem to eat much at lunch.
You should have some.
Okay.
And you crossed the line earlier.
You used me.
I know that
you like Ms. Joo In-a.
I'm a very competent assistant
and a woman who likes you.
Ki-jun is
a great guy.
It was the first time I ran away
feeling annoyed
that he found out about my situation
and I didn't want to burden him.
I didn't want to be
belittled before him.
Why are you telling me this?
I'm saying you have nothing on Ki-jun
even for someone like you.
HR REPORT
ON US EXPATRIATE
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- Two toasts, please.
- Sure.
- Please make them delicious.
- Of course.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
What is this?
What does he have to say now?
HR HEAD AHN SEUNG-WOO, PERVERT
MISSED CALLS FROM
Your call cannot be connected.
You will be redirected to voicemail.
ASSISTANT MANAGER NOH KI-JUN
Will you please pick up?
Hey, Ki-jun!
What's going on, man?
You really got
on the vice president's good side.
What are you talking about?
Ms. Hong of HR told me everything.
I heard you got assigned
as an expatriate to the US.
What?
I'm so jealous.
Your call cannot be connected.
You will be redirected to voicemail.
Goodness, Mr. Lee. Mr. Lee.
Thank you for coming out
on your busy day.
Yes.
I can't have you keep calling me.
Think of how desperate I am.
I'm about to get divorced.
My wife is now...
She's banning me
from seeing my child, Do-yun.
Can you help me
get a favorable arrangement
or let me settle the case?
Maybe the employees
can turn in petitions
and say that I've worked hard
and always had a great reputation.
Well, even if I
personally made a move
the Audit Team
is already set on this.
I've also been
contacting Mr. Noh Ki-jun
but he won't pick up his phone.
Mr. Ahn, he's on a roll right now.
He got a special promotion,
thanks to your incident
and he even got a chance
to work in the US.
You didn't know?
Director Park, I hear your daughter
is getting married soon.
Congratulations.
Let me know when you have the date.
I'd like to relay
my congratulatory message.
Goodness, Director Park.
That wedding will be a big deal.
Are you really willing to come
and share a message?
Or do you think
a song will be better?
Your call cannot be connected.
You will be redirected to voicemail.
Why won't she pick up?
JOO IN-A
Your call cannot be connected.
You will be redirected to voicemail.
Hey, have you seen Ms. Joo?
Have you seen her?
I didn't, but Seung-hee just told me
that Ms. Joo suddenly showed up
and left with the vice president.
Where did they go?
What do you think you're doing?
- What?
- About Mr. Noh Ki-jun!
You did not say a word to him or me,
who has direct authority over him.
How can you suddenly announce
sending him away overnight
like he's some parcel?
And you barged in there
to nitpick over this?
You dragged me out
of a meeting with the directors
just to nitpick over
an assistant manager's position?
It's not just his position.
This is a matter of respect
for my duty and authority.
You are not allowed
to appoint an employee like this
if he has no reason
to be disciplined.
This is unjust.
And this calls for an audit.
I've reviewed
the decision thoroughly.
It's a loss to the business
for an employee with his performance
and competence
to be cooped up doing PM duties.
Is that really the reason
and not because
of any personal feelings?
It's the US expatriate position.
That's a place
where every employee wants to go
and it's a privilege
for an assistant manager.
He'll also be promoted as a manager.
Is this something
for you to be so angry over?
In-a, don't you think
you're the one holding back
a talented employee's career
because of your feelings?
Can you honestly tell me
that you are this furious
only due to official reasons?
In-a.
There are many decisions I can make.
And among them, I believe I made
the most courteous one I could.
Your call cannot be connected.
You will be redirected to voicemail.
Mr. Noh Ki-jun.
Mr. Ahn.
I cannot have you visit
or contact me like this.
Hey, you...
EMERGENCY ROOM
You can't drive like this.
Let me take you there.
Is he still waiting
in the emergency room?
No, it's okay. There's no need.
I'll call you back.
I'll just get off here.
It's still pretty far from here.
Just past the intersection... In-a!
It's heartbreaking.
You must've been very lonely.
You keep acting tough
which is making it worse.
Then will you
answer my question...
Why do you push me away?
About your question, Mr. Noh...
The real reason
why I keep pushing you away...
I...
FILING FOR LOVE
Mr. Noh. I was scared. It was scary.
I think you should come along
to the Jeju business trip, Ms. Joo.
What are you doing?
Are you sending an assistant manager
overseas because of your feelings?
In-a, please just stay by my side.
What's the real reason you sent me
to Audit Team Three?
Was it to protect Jeon Jae-yeol?
How do you expect me
to understand this whole situation?
We need to talk right now!
Oddly enough
I have a habit of hiding the truth
when it matters most.
Subtitles by Eunsook Youn
and Jennifer Lim